today we're going to do a Bane and
Company round one case for those of you
who don't know me my name is Matt and
I'm a current seconde associate at BCG
which is a management consulting firm I
make these videos because I enjoy it but
also because I would have wish that
somebody would have made these for me
when I was younger today I'm going to be
walking you through a bane and& company
round one case and showing you my
thought process so that hopefully you
can tackle this type of case on your own
and one caveat I want to make before we
get into this video is that for best
results you should attempt this Cas on
your own before looking through my
explanation but if maybe it's your first
time doing this or you're too
intimidated to try it on your own then
just keep watching let's get into it so
the case that we're going to look at
today is called National Logistics it's
representative of a bane round one case
and the prompt reads as follows your
client is National Logistics a large
transportation and logistics company
that delivers fright to all areas of
North America Over The Last 5 Years the
company has experienced Rising costs due
to increases in wages resulting from a
shortage of truckers the client is now
looking to reduce operational costs in
the business how would you advise the
client okay so the first thing we want
to do whenever we hear the prompt is we
want to be taking quick notes and after
we take notes we want to basically
restate our understanding of the
situation to the interviewer and also
ask a few clarifying questions and so
I'm going to just take a few seconds now
and take some quick
notes all right
so our client
is National
Logistics they basically deliver
fright all over North
America and Over The Last 5
Years cost cost s
have
increased due to
wages and so there's been a
shortage of
truckers question is how to
reduce
costs
okay and so after I take quick notes the
first thing you always want to do is you
want to restate to the interviewer your
understanding of the situation and also
to make sure that you haven't missed out
on any crucial details and so the way I
would go about this is I would say okay
great so it sounds like our client is
National Logistics they're a fright and
shipping company based primarily in
North America and so the problem that
they're facing over the last 5 years is
that due to a shortage of truckers in
the overall transportation and fright
industry their wages have had to
increase to attract you know a
sufficient number of drivers and so
they're asking us today how can we
reduce our operational costs to the
business uh which would thereby increase
profitability and so the next thing you
want to do is you want to have a few key
questions prepared and as I mentioned
earlier it's really important to ask
these questions um for a couple of
reasons but mainly because you also want
to demonstrate to the interviewer that
you are paying attention and that you're
thinking thoughtfully about the question
so even if you maybe don't have any
pressing or burning questions you should
try to come up with at least one or two
questions to clar the situation so a few
clarifying questions that I can think
off off the top of my head for example
is uh you know
geographically are we
limited to North
America
or is there any plans for potentially
International
expansion and then the interviewer might
say no we're primarily a North America
based company
we want to stay in the same geography
there's no plans to go abroad now you
could also
ask have they tried
anything
already to lower
costs because this is going to help us
understand has the company even tried
anything before and how they're
currently thinking about the problem
because maybe management has been
thinking about this a lot and maybe they
have tried a few things but have been
unsuccessful which is why they've
brought us on or you know they maybe
have not tried anything and they just
want us to help them brainstorm a few
directions that they could take so
another question as I said we could ask
is have they tried anything already and
the interviewer might say no they
haven't tried anything yet management
has only recently come to realize that
costs were increasing so dramatically
over the last 5 years and therefore they
want us to think about as many options
as possible to lower operational costs
and I guess just to be holistic we can
try to think of a third clarifying
question here and so we could ask
something like are there any other costs
that are
rising because we know for a fact that
wages in the trucking industry have been
going up due to this shortage but is
there any other cost that is
contributing to this increase in
operational costs for Trucking and
shipping businesses right because maybe
wages is number one but maybe number two
is something else and so we just want to
be very sure that we're looking in the
right
places and so in response to this you
know the interviewer might say something
like yeah there are a few other you know
Rising costs to the business like you
know having to repair and maintain the
fleet the costs have gone up recently
but not as significant as the increases
in wages over the last 5 years and so
that would tell you that hey we really
need to be looking into the wages
specifically but uh as like a secondary
area to look we can look into other
costs like for example maintaining and
repairing their Fleet of trucks okay
okay but now that we've asked our
clarifying questions the next thing you
want to immediately do is you want to
start coming up with your framework and
so the way you want to go about this is
you want to ask the interviewer for 60
to 90 seconds to come up with a
framework how you would do this is you
would say okay great can I just take 60
seconds to structure my thoughts and the
interviewer will always say yes and this
is your cue to kind of go ahead and take
some time to think through a
framework and the interviewer will
always say
okay so I've spent about a minute or two
putting together a quick framework and
for this case I'm just using a simple
profitability esque framework so
basically the two main buckets that I've
segmented out here are sales uh as well
as costs and and so just to walk you
through how you should approach
presenting this to the interviewer you
always want to be super clear about the
different buckets that you have and you
want to lay it out to them in an
extremely logical Manner and so it might
sound a little bit like robotic almost
to say it like this but the way you want
to do this is you want to be super
structured and you want to say so the
way that I'm thinking about this is I've
kind of segmented the two main areas
that I want to understand a little bit
more the first is on the revenue side of
things I want to understand that a
little bit more and then the second is
the the cost side of the equation and
I've included both revenue and costs
even though the question is primarily
what can we do to costs because I think
revenue and costs are linked and all
both contribute to profitability which I
understand as probably being the
ultimate goal for the company and so
going back to the first bucket sales
here I've broken this out into two
buckets one being pricing and the second
being volume and then under costs I've
broken the costs into two smaller
buckets of fixed costs versus variable
costs and so I'll talk a little bit
about each of these buckets so under
Revenue with pricing here I really want
to understand you know a little bit more
about our pricing structure how are we
actually pricing each shipment is it on
a I would assume that we have some sort
of contract with our clients so a
business for example that wants to ship
its goods around the US would come to us
and then we would therefore sign a
contract with them saying hey you're
going to pay us either on a per shipment
basis so every shipment or maybe you're
going to pay us some sort of combination
of a fixed fee plus a variable fee based
on how much volume we're shipping for
you or maybe based on the weight of the
shipments that we're actually moving for
you but I really want to better
understand how exactly we are pricing
our shipments on the volume side I want
to understand a little bit more about
you know the number of deliveries the
volume of deliveries as well as the
number of drivers that we currently have
and any historical and projected trends
for those stats and also on volume I'm
kind of interested in what is the
average volume in a given shipment and
the reason I bring this up is because
maybe a lot of trucks and a lot of
shipments are going out without Max
Capacity maybe they're only being 50%
utilized and so maybe there's an
opportunity to potentially pack each
shipment full with more boxes or more
products but moving to the cost side of
things on the fixed cost side here I
just want to better understand you know
what are the main sources of fixed costs
here one that I can think of immediately
is any overhead costs related to you
know the corporate side of the business
so salaries wages rent for the offices
things like that I just want to
understand that a little bit better and
whether there's any leeway to lower
those costs side note this is kind of
one of the buckets that people think of
when they think of Consultants going in
and Advising to lay off a lot of staff
at big companies because a major source
of costs can be within overhead the
wages and the salary packages for the
employees in the corporate side of the
business but moving to the variable side
uh here I've kind of broken it out into
a few main buckets the first being labor
costs which we've mentioned understand
that the wages for drivers has been
increasing over time but wanted to
include that to be holistic second any
input costs related to actually making
the shipments so these would be things
like fuel for example anything that
basically increases as you drive a
longer distance to complete a shipment
and so these are also things like
maintenance costs related to repairing
your trucks for example because every I
don't know 100,000 miles maybe a truck
breaks down and so you need to invest a
certain amount of money into repairing
that truck or replacing it um and then
finally I've included this kind of other
bucket which would include miscellaneous
costs that also are variable like toll
fees because if you are driving on the
highway for example you might need to
pay certain fees to drive on different
roads but that's kind of a catchall
bucket to include any other potential
variable costs that we could look at
okay so after this you would basically
want to stop and get the interviewer's
thoughts on this framework and sometimes
they will point you in a certain
direction and they'll say great let's
talk about pricing for example but other
times they might not give you as much
Direction and they might say something
like awesome so where would you suggest
we start first and this is where don't
be intimidated they're just opening up
the conversation for you and you should
just think about which of these buckets
you think is most interesting or
potentially might be most important for
this project fully understanding that
the goal with a framework is always
typically to go through every single
bucket in the framework until you've
gotten to the root cause of the problem
and so say for example in this question
I'm really interested in specifically
the trucks and how we can lower costs
related to the trucks whether that be
the fuel costs related to the trucks or
the maintenance costs so maybe that
means is there a possibility to invest
in more highquality fleets that are also
more fuel efficient and so what I would
say to the interviewer is the first area
I want to look into is really
investigating the fleet a little bit
more is there any opportunity has
management explored the possibility of
potentially investing in a more fuel
efficient Fleet and the interviewer
would give you some feedback on that now
obviously I know the answer to this case
and so I'm I'm guiding Us in the right
direction but if the interviewer says
for example no they haven't done
anything but there's no plans to look
into that in the future or they've
already kind of ruled it out as a
possibility then don't fret just go back
to your framework and ask them about the
second bucket that you find most
interesting and eventually you'll get
there but in this case the interviewer
is going to tell us that uh yes we have
some data actually related to the cost
of operating Each truck and so they're
going to flash this exhibit up on the
screen and the first thing you always
want to do is you want to basically
before you even think about okay what
does this even mean you want to talk
aloud and explain what you're actually
seeing and so how I would go about this
is I would say oh awesome so it looks
like we have some Financial metrics
related to these standard trucks that we
currently have as well as these new
hybrid trucks which are supposedly more
fuel efficient and so we've been given
the purchase price maintenance year
Insurance year average miles driven per
year miles per gallon vehicle lifespan
and right off the bat I can see that the
hybrid trucks are obviously a lot more
expensive because their purchase price
is you know 50% higher they're $150,000
per truck uh but at the same time they
are twice as fuel effici efficient and
so the miles per gallon is 20 as opposed
to 10 for the standard truck and you
know the lifespan looks to be about the
same but the overall costs for the
hybrid trucks appear to be higher and I
see that National Express pays an
average of $3 per gallon per fuel okay
so we have some metrics related to cost
for each gallon and so after you've
given your initial observations about
the table you want to start thinking
about any potential questions or
analyses that you can run with this data
set that could potentially lead to any
sort of conclusion but usually the
interviewer will start guiding you
towards the calculation or the question
that they actually want to see and so in
this particular case the question would
be we ran two cost scenarios for the
client to compare the cost of operating
a hybrid truck versus a standard diesel
truck what are the potential cost
savings if any from switching to a
hybrid truck and so I'm going to start
just writing some of the costs down from
the exhibit onto my paper just so I can
start thinking through how I might be
able to calculate this first thing we
have is
maintenance which for standard is
5K a
year and then for hybrid it's 8K a
year
insurance is 2K a year for
standard 3K a year for
hybrid and so just totaling those up is
already 7K a year
for standard 11k a
year for
hybrid and then there
is other our costs related to fuel so
the average miles
driven for a standard truck is
60,000 and for a hybrid truck it's also
60,000 and we basically want to divide
that by our miles per
gallon which is 10 and
20 and so that's basically
six and then multiply by basically the
cost per gallon which in this case is $3
okay so on the standard side we have
60,000 M divided by 10 m per gallon so
that gets us about 6,000 time $3 per
gallon so 6,000 * 3 is
$18,000 and then on the hybrid side we
have 60,000 M driven divided by 20 m per
gallon which gets us about 3,000 3,000 *
$3 per gallon is
9,000 and so right now it looks like our
costs are just you know the maintenance
plus the insurance plus the fuel costs
but something that we haven't talked
about yet is related to the life of each
truck and that is depreciation expense
for those you who don't know if you
haven't taken an account in class
depreciation expense is basically just a
expense related to the age of the
vehicle if you're confused about
depreciation the way you can think about
it is just look if I buy a car for
example the value of that car is going
to decrease each year and so you know a
10-year-old car is not going to be worth
the same as a brand new car right and so
how do you account for that on the
financial statements well it's through
something called depreciation expense
and so
a good thing to mention here to the
interviewer in this situation would be
to just ask like if you're unsure
whether or not you should be thinking
about this you should literally just
bring it up because the worst thing they
can say is no you don't need to factor
that into your calculation and you want
that to happen as opposed to you
forgetting to ask or just assuming that
it's not necessary and then it messes up
your answer and so I would ask the
interviewer hey I noticed that we might
need to account for a depreciation
expense can I assume you know straight
line depreciation for the purposes of
this of this case straight line
depreciation is just when you divide the
purchase price of that vehicle by the
number of years that it is useful so in
this case we know the useful life is the
vehicle lifespan of 10 years and so we
would just divide the purchase price for
the standard truck which is
$100,000 by 10 years to get us to a
depreciation expense
of $10,000
sorry if this is really
messy
and on the hybrid truck side we have a
purchase price of
$150,000 divide that by 10 years so it's
about 15K of depreciation there and so
our total costs are
actually this
plus this plus this
okay which comes
out to 11 + 9 is 20 20 + 15 is 35 35
K
7 + 18 is 25 + 10 is
35 so this is really interesting what we
can see here is that the cost base for
each of these trucks is roughly equal
and so right off the bat alarm Bells
should be going off in your head you
should be wondering first of all this is
really interesting but why and what does
this mean in the context of our project
but you also always want to be telling
the interviewer what you're thinking
about and what you're seeing and so
right off the bat you should say well
this is really interesting what I'm
seeing here is that the costs for the
standard truck and the hybrid truck are
actually about $35,000 per year each and
so there is no annual cost savings with
using either of these at least from a
numerical perspective there's no benefit
and so you want to talk to the
interviewer about your findings and you
want to talk them through what's going
through your head so you want to tell
them something like as I mentioned it
looks like there are no Associated cost
savings or cost advantage to using a
standard truck versus a hybrid truck at
least from a numerical perspective
there's no reason for us to adopt this
hybrid Fleet but that said there
potentially may be other reasons more
qualitative reasons why you might want
to use a hybrid truck as opposed to a
standard semi- truck maybe for example
the hybrid truck has a greater carrying
capacity for the loads that we want to
bring right cuz that would indirectly
lower our number of shipments needed to
deliver or complete a trip you always
want to think Beyond just the initial
finding because there's often a second
or third level of insight that may not
be apparent right off the bat from just
looking at the numbers but in this case
the interviewer would say to you great
well given the results of the analysis
would you recommend for National
Logistics to invest in hybrid trucks why
or why not so the question is should
they invest in hybrid
trucks and here I think it's okay to ask
for another 30 seconds to Think Through
Your Response here because again you've
been given a lot of data already and and
information and sometimes it helps to
just take a few seconds to process that
information and as long as you're not
taking too long here most interviewers
would be okay okay with you taking a few
seconds to just put together some good
thoughts so what I'm actually going to
do here is I'm going to put together
like a yes versus a no column and so
under yes we can think of like potential
ideas why you might want to invest in
hybrid trucks and under no you would
basically think through reasons that you
might not want to invest in hybrid
trucks this way we can have a little bit
more of a holistic perspective on both
the reasons that someone would or would
not do this
okay so what I've done here is I've
taken some time to really think through
potential reasons why someone would want
to invest in these hybrid trucks versus
would not want to and so I'll walk you
through each of my thinking behind each
and so the first bullet under the yes
bucket here it reads hybrid trucks may
be superior in some other way and so my
thinking here was essentially there
could be some other intangible advantage
that we just can't see in the numbers
that hybrid trucks have for example a
hybrid truck may be able to carry more
boxes as I mentioned earlier in this
video and that would be a huge benefit
if that were true also maybe it's more
efficient in some other way and would
allow the shipment time to decrease now
you might be wondering how is this
possible well one thing I can think of
is we can also think about the driver's
time as being a source of efficiency so
maybe these trucks are better in terms
of navigation maybe they have better
built-in navigation systems that would
allow us to complete trips in a shorter
amount of time things like that and so
you really would want to ask the
interviewer here like hey is there any
information about these trucks that
would potentially differentiate them in
a real big way like this and based on
their response you can decide whether or
not this is impactful or not but the
goal here is you always want to be
thinking again as I said beyond just
what the numbers show you and think
about any other reasons that could
potentially make it a good reason to
invest in this new Fleet A good rule of
thumb with casing in general is you
always want to think about both sides of
the coin so even when there is a
conclusion or an analysis or a data set
that's shown to you that appears to
demonstrate a very clear conclusion or
something that to you might seem like oh
that's a no-brainer right but you always
want to stop and take a few seconds to
think about okay well what if I'm not
right what if the answer is the other
side of the coin why would that be what
are some potential reasons why someone
who's taking the opposite side of what I
think is right would use to back up
their argument and if you get in the
habit of thinking like that you're not
only going to be very good at the job
but you're also going to just get very
good at casing but moving on to the
second bullet under yes I also wrote
more efficient and economical if fuel
prices increase now what do I mean by
this well let's go back up and look at
our numbers here based on the numbers
that we were given we concluded right
that there was no cost benefit because
it was $35,000 per year in costs for
both a standard truck and a hybrid truck
now most people would have stopped here
and they would have just accepted this
as okay that's the end I'll be
right but if we look a little bit closer
at the numbers we can see that in this
scenario the maintenance and insurance
costs appear to be pretty fixed right
they're not going to change too much on
a yearly basis the depreciation expense
is also not going to change that much on
a yearly basis unless something changes
about like the price or the average
useful life of each truck but when it
comes to the fuel prices This is highly
variable because it's dependent on three
things it's dependent on how many miles
are being driven by each truck it's
dependent on the miles per gallon and
it's also dependent on the cost per
gallon and if we look at all three of
these things let's change colors here in
the scenario that we were given it was
$3 per gallon but just for argument sake
let's assume that the price per gallon
doubled and so suddenly instead of $3
per gallon this went up to let's say
six
okay now what would happen to to our
total costs
well our maintenance and insurance costs
would stay the same miles driven let's
just assume that stays the same as
well and miles per gallon that's not
going to change and so what's our total
cost what's the change to our total
costs well we still have our 7,000 per
year of Maintenance and
insurance plus our new fuel cost now of
36,000 which is roughly 43,000 plus 10
which is 53,000 so this
if you're still following along goes to
53k okay and then what happens to our
hybrid well we have still our 11,000 of
Maintenance and insurance but plus now a
new 18,000 in fuel which is roughly
44,000 if I did my math correctly call
me out if I didn't but now you can see
that there is a
difference and that the hybrid truck is
actually more worth if the fuel price
increases and so this is where it's a
little bit more nuanced than we might
have realized before because if the cost
of fuel increases then it's worth it to
use our hybrid trucks but on the other
hand if let's say the cost per gallon
decreased below $3 per gallon then what
would happen well the opposite would
happen and actually the standard diesel
trucks would be more economical than
these expensive hybrid trucks and so
this is why if we believe that that the
cost of fuel is going to increase then
it makes sense from a financial
perspective to invest in hybrid trucks
but if we believe that the cost of fuel
is going to decrease over time then it
makes sense to stick with normal trucks
because they're going to cost less and
so there's no right answer here the goal
of this kind of question is really to
test your thinking and whatever you
present as you know your recommendation
of should we invest in these hybrid
trucks or not to the interviewer just
make sure that it's backed up by data
and a clear reasonable line of thinking
so that they can see like how you think
about this kind of question I still
haven't talked through all the no
buckets but just to go through them
quickly I essentially wrote down you
know no cost benefit from the analysis
but then I I sort of talked what through
you know why this would change based on
the fuel price and so I had no more
economical if fuel decreases and then
the last bullet that I had here was you
know higher maintenance expenses if you
use these hybrid trucks because if you
remember if we scroll back up here it's
$8,000 a year and it's also more
expensive from an insurance perspective
actually so I should note that down and
often times these newer more
technologically advanced Vehicles like
if you think about electric cars for
example like a Tesla the parts can be
quite expensive and difficult to
maintain because traditional auto shops
or uh dealers or repair repair stores
just don't have the specialized parts
for EVS that they would have for
traditional diesel or uh you know gas
vehicles and so that's another thing to
consider as well okay but let's take a
step back and so after we've put
together this list of yes and NOS we
would then want to basically explain to
the interviewer each of these points
that I've just explained to you and so
the way I would do this is I would say
okay great so I've put together a few
points supporting but also going against
the use of these hybrid trucks and
before I make a recommendation as to
whether I think we should or should not
I just want to lay these out so that you
can fully understand what my thought
process is and what's going through my
mind and they'll say okay great go for
it and then you'll talk through each of
these points really quickly don't ramble
too much just keep it high level and
then finally talk about you know whether
you think you should invest in hybrid
trucks or not and in this scenario I'm
just going to pick the no bucket uh
because I'm going to assume that the
hybrid trucks were not Superior in any
other way they you know they couldn't
carry more boxes for example they
weren't more efficient and so and I also
didn't think that the fuel prices were
going to increase by that dramatically
given the current economic environment
and so let's just say that I went with
no and so I would say okay great so and
based on my understanding of all of
these points I would still recommend
against investing in hybrid trucks and
because I don't believe that the fuel
prices are going to increase that
dramatically over the long term and also
because the hybrid trucks are much more
expensive and also because there's
minimal advantage to using the hybrid
trucks from an efficiency and carrying
capacity perspective and so I don't
believe that at least right now it makes
sense for us to invest upfront in these
more costly trucks and so just stop
there and get the interviewer's thoughts
but usually after this the interviewer
will start guiding you to the next part
of the question which in this case is
the brainstorm and so the brainstorming
problem reads the client also wants to
get our thoughts on how they can reduce
their shortage of truckers brainstorm
some ways National Logistics can reduce
their shortage okay so brainstorming
sections are quite common in case
interviews and they're really there to
test your ability to just come up with
ideas on the spot and it's not so much
about coming up with the right answer as
it is coming up with a wellth thought
out array of different answers or
different solutions and so don't be
afraid also to take a few seconds here
as well to come up with a few ideas if
you don't feel like you can just come up
with things on the Fly and so I would
ask the interviewer hey can I take just
another 30 seconds to put together some
thoughts and they would of course say
yes so let's do that okay so I've thrown
together a few ideas here that I'll just
walk you through and in no particular
order some things that the company could
do here to reduce the trigger short
shortage is one they could obviously try
to increase wages but here we know that
that probably not going to be a very
feasible alternative I've just put it
here to be holistic but two they could
also create other sorts of incentives to
really attract people to work at the
company and to retain their current
employees and so these would could be
things like you know benefits for
existing employees maybe that's
increasing PTO or better health
insurance better parental leave policies
or more flexible vacation policies for
example maybe there's even like bonuses
that truckers can get for successfully
completing X number of routs in x amount
of time for example just throwing ideas
out out there you could also create some
sort of promotion to attract new people
to become drivers whether that's like a
referral bonus for your current
employees like hey we'll pay you $4,000
if you refer a friend who gets hired to
work at this trucking company or also
you know promotions that attract people
to come work at your company like hey
join this Trucking Company where you're
going to have better benefits than your
competitors and then the final thing
that you can also do is you can go
beyond just your company and look
outside and you could hire a thirdparty
fleet of truckers to support increased
demand during the holiday season for
example or whenever you have any sort of
shortages these are just a few ideas
that you could think of the goal here is
you just want to throw out as many ideas
as you can and talk the interviewer
through each idea but finally we've come
to the conclusion of the case and so at
the end of every case the interviewer
will usually ask you to synthesize your
findings and synthesis is basically just
looking through everything that you've
learned today and summing it all up in a
very concise recommendation in like 30
seconds and so the typical way that it's
presented to you here would be imagine
that the CEO of the company is walking
down the hall and you're in a conference
room and you have about 30 seconds to
Think Through what you would say to the
CEO and what you would recommend them
what would you tell them and so you can
take about like 20 to 30 seconds to
really think through and this is where I
usually like to scroll back up and look
through my notes and really think
through everything that I've learned
today right and a helpful format that I
like to follow and that other colleagues
of mine have also recommended is you
always want to start with a quick
restatement of the problem State your
findings you want to provide a
recommendation and then you want to
provide some risks and finally end with
next steps and so I know that seems like
kind of a lot but the way that this
would sound in practice is a lot more
succinct and so this is how I would go
about it awesome so as a reminder we
were tasked with thinking about how we
could lower the operational costs of the
business and what we found is through
our analysis of the different trucking
options and paths forward there is
currently no Advantage from a cost
perspective of investing in a hybrid
Fleet as opposed to a standard Fleet
however this can change based on the
fuel prices in the future but since we
don't see fuel prices increasing
dramatically over the long term we
recommend sticking with a standard Fleet
because it's more economical at lower
fuel prices and we also recommend
implementing policies to increase driver
retention and attract new truckers to
alleviate the shortage as well as hiring
outside help to support the heavy season
now that said the risk to this strategy
is obviously gas prices potentially
increasing more than we anticipate as
well as the possibility that our
policies or our incentive programs may
not work as well as planned and we may
run into a potential driver shortage or
potentially that hiring outside help may
be more costly than anticipated but as a
potential next step we would recommend
looking into the cost of hiring outside
help just to analyze what it would take
to really bring on that outside help and
how feasible the implementation of that
would be as well as the other policies
that we've mentioned with driving user
retention and also implementing a new
standard Fleet of trucks okay so that
was the case I hope this was helpful and
I'll see you guys in the next one